Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Issues: United States: Finance (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 43)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Issues: United States: Foreign relations, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 44)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Issues: United States: Foreign trade (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 45)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Issues: United States: Politics (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 46)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Issues: United States: W (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 47)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Issues: United States: Women (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 48)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: News coverage (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 49)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Polls (Offsite-box 1973, Folder 50)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Primaries (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Recounts (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Runoffs (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 3)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Trends, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Trends: Agriculture (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 5)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Trends: Independent voters (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Trends: Labor (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Trends: Minorities (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Trends: Women (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1986: Trends: Youth (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985 (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Campaign (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Candidates (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 13)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Candidates: Who's for whom (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 14)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Finance (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Frauds (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Gubernatorial (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Mayoral (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 19)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: News coverage (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Recounts (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Runoffs (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1985: Trends (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 25-27)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Campaign, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 28-32)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Candidates, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 33-36)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Candidates: Who's for whom, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1974, Folder 37-38)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Candidates: Who's for whom, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 1-2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Congressional, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 3-6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Elections: 1984: Conventions (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Finance, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Foreign reactions, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Frauds, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Gambling (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Gubernatorial (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 13-17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: A (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Abortion, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 19-22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Agriculture (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Atomic weapons, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Automobile industry (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 25)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: B (Offsite-box 1975, Folder 26)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: C, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: D, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Disarmament and atomic control, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 3-4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: E, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 5)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Education, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Environment, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: F, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: I, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: J (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: G (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: H (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: L, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 13)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: M (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 14)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Missiles, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: N (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: O (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: P, 1983 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Q (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 19)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: R (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Religion (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: S, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Social Security, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Social welfare (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: T (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 25)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Taxes, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1976, Folder 26-28)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Taxes, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 1-2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: U (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 3)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Unemployment, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 5)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: Unions (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Armed forces (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Courts (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Diplomatic services (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Economics, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 10-11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Finance, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 12-15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Foreign relations, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 16-18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Foreign trade, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 19)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Government (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Immigration and emigration, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Industries, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Politics (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Population (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: Public works (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 25)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: V (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 26)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Issues: United States: W (Offsite-box 1977, Folder 27)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: News coverage, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 1978, Folder 1-7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Platforms (Offsite-box 1978, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Polls, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 1978, Folder 9-15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Primaries, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 1978, Folder 16-23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Primaries, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Recounts, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Runoffs (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 3)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: State and local caucuses and conventions, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 4-6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: Agriculture (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: Independent voters, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: Labor, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 10-16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: Minorities, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 17-20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: Press, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: State (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: Women, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1984: Trends: Youth, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 25)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Candidates (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 26)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Candidates: Who's for whom (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 27)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Congressional, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 28)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Finance, 1986-1986 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 29)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Frauds (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 30)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Gubernatorial (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 31)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Issues (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 32)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Mayoral (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 33)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: News coverage (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 34)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Recounts (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 35)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Runoffs (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 36)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1983: Trends, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 37)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 38)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Campaign (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 39)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Candidates (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 40)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Candidates: Who's for whom, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 41)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Congressional, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2006, Folder 42-45)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Congressional, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 1-4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Finance, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 5)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Foreign reactions (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Frauds, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Gubernatorial (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: A-Z (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: Crime (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: Disarmament and atomic control (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: Social Security (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 13)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: Taxes (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 14)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: Unemployment, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: United States: Economics, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 16-19)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: United States: Finance (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: United States: News coverage (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: United States: Platform (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: United States: Polls (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Issues: United States: Primaries (Offsite-box 2007, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Recounts (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Reruns (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Runoffs (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 3)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: Agriculture (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 5)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: Independent voters (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: Labor (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: Minorities (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: Press (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: State (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: Women (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1982: Trends: Youth (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 13)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Campaign (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 14)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Candidates: Image, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Candidates: Who's for whom, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Finance, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Frauds (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Gubernatorial (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 19)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Issues (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Mayoral (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: News coverage (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Polls (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Recounts (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Runoffs (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 25)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1981: Trends, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 26)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 27)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Campaign, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 2008, Folder 28-39)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Campaign, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 2009, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Candidates, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 2009, Folder 2-8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Candidates: Who's for whom, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 2009, Folder 9-12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Congressional, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 2009, Folder 13-16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Conventions, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2009, Folder 17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Finance, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 2009, Folder 18-20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Finance, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Foreign reactions, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 2-4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Frauds, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 5)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Gambling (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Gubernatorial, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 8-11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: A, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: Abortion (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 13)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: Atomic energy, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 14)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: B (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: C (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: D, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: E, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: Energy and fuel, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 19)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: F (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: G, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: H, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: I, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: Inflation, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2010, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: L, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: M, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: N, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 3)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: O, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: P, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 5)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: R (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: S, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 7)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: T, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 8)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: U, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: United States: Armed forces, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: United States: Economics, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 11-14)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: United States: Foreign relations, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: United States: Foreign trade (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: United States: Government, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2011, Folder 18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: United States: Industries (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: United States: Population (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: V (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 3)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Issues: W, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 4)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: News coverage, 1976-1985 (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 5-9)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Platforms (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Polls, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 11-18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Primaries, 1976-1981 (Offsite-box 2012, Folder 19-25)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Recounts (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 1)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Reruns (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 2)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Runoffs (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 3)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: State and local caucuses and conventions, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 4-6)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 7-10)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: Agriculture (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 11)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: Independent voters (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 12)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: Labor (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 13)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: Minorities, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 14)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: Press, 1976-1981 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 15)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: State (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 16)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: Women (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 17)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1980: Trends: Youth, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 18)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 19)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Campaign, 1978 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 20)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Candidates: Who's for whom (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 21)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Congressional (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 22)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Finance, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 23)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Finance: Corporate contributions, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 24)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Frauds (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 25)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Gubernatorial (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 26)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Issues (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 27)
  - United States: Politics: Elections: 1979: Mayoral (Offsite-box 2013, Folder 28)